翻译　水平有限的皮带断了
多年来 在游轮公司有个不成文的政策
For a number of years, there was an unofficial company policy
字　　幕　　侠
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
后期　Jason肖　特效　小布
如果发生了严重的犯罪事件
on Cruise Lines that if there was a serious criminal incident,
ZIMUXIA.CN
校对　水平有限的皮带断了　时间轴　阿布
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
我们可以大事化小 避免消极公关
we could minimize the incident to avoid negative PR.
压制　Jason肖
监制　水平有限的皮带断了
-怎样的犯罪事件...  -偷窃 性侵 谋杀
- Incidents like... - Theft. Sexual assault. Murder.
ZIMUXIA.CN
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
好吧 坏事件
Okay. The bad ones.
没错 这里有数百起
Yeah. There's hundreds in there.
你只需要签领一些文件盒出来
All you have to do is sign out some boxes.
绞碎几张纸 见几位善良的人
Do a little bit of shredding. Meet some lovely guys.
只是小事一桩 格雷格
It's not a big deal, Greg!
我们需要这个
We need this.
拿下皮尔斯是我们代理权防御的关键
Bagging Pierce is the key to our proxy defense.
你有没有想过 把钥匙交给谁[谁做接班人]
Any thought given to whom you might hand over the keys?
我真的不喜欢假设
I really don't like to deal in hypotheticals.
看在他妈的上天份上 爸爸 告诉他们会是我
For fuck's sake, Dad. Just tell them its gonna be me.
我们言归正传
Here we are.
我们想同时宣布并购
We want to announce the sale and Shiv
和小西接班的消息 要么就没有交易
at the same time, or there's no deal.
这不是我做事的方式
That's not quite how I do things.
我可以出到250亿 但是 必须很快完成交易
I could go to 25, but it would have to be fast.
那 这样的话...同意
Then in that case... Yes.
这他妈的太对了
That's goddamn fucking right!
敬我们自己
Here's to us.
钱赢了
Money wins.
那 飞行员明确说了 还要半个小时
So, pilot apparently says another half hour.
跑道很紧俏 400架喷气飞机分享100条跑道
It's just slots, it's, 400 jets fighting over 100 spaces.
如果我发现一些高科技混蛋在我们之前降落
If I find some tech fuck gets landed before us,
我会杀了他们的 好吗
I'm gonna kill 'em. Okay?
我们搞定了吗
We okay?
他们还在确定皮尔斯交易的分手费
On the Pierce deal they're entrenching on the break fee.
费用非常非常巨量
Very, very aggressive.
好吧 去他妈的 对吧
Well, fuck 'em, right?
我的意思是 他们就是些徒有其表的家伙 他们现在不会转身而去的
I mean, they're empty suits, they're not gonna walk away now.
也许...
Maybe...
也许我们应该满足他们的要求
Maybe we just give them what they want.
我们应该满足他们的要求
We just give 'em what they want?
对不起 爸爸 我想你会气得再次中风的
Excuse me, Dad, I think you just had another stroke.
我今天就想签订协议
I wanna sign here. Today.
好吧 我觉得有一个问题是
Well, I think the one thing is just,
就团队而言 他们可能会
there could just be a burnout issue
-产生倦怠...  - 不
- in terms of the teams... - No!
肯 你去吧 我累了
Ken, go. I'm tired.
让他们记牢了 我昨天就需要搞定这件事的
Impress upon them that I need this done yesterday.
好的
Okay.
我们他妈的一直盘旋了一小时了
We've been circling for a fucking hour.
你们什么时候能把协议交给我
When can we expect something in my hand?
-很快了  -具体什么时候
- Imminently. - Like when?
快了 为了保密 防止泄露
Soon. For confidentiality, leak protection,
我们保持小圈子
we kept the circle small.
-每个人都很分散  -这他妈不够好
- Everyone's spread pretty thin. - It's not fucking good enough.
你他妈的在这糊弄我呢
You're fucking me here.
我他妈的正在取得
I'm making good faith fucking assessments
我爸的信任 你让我看起来像个混蛋
to my father, and you're making me look like a hack,
我是不会接受的
and I will not have it.
别他妈在这里互相吹捧了
Stop sucking each other off back here,
赶紧给我搞出来
and get fucking on it.
你把我安排给你的任务
You pour the shit I'm pouring on you
安排给你的狗腿子们 然后驱赶他们好好干
on your fucking minions, and you ride them.
我不在乎你怎么干  全天不休还是轮班
I don't care. 24 hours, rolling shifts,
用他妈的鞭子狠狠地催
crack the fuckin' whip.
你正在做的一切都是他妈的狗屁
Everything you're doing is fucking bullshit,
而且我对你很失望
and I'm very disappointed in you.
我对天发誓 如果你继续瞎鸡巴胡闹
I swear to God, I will fucking fire you
我他妈会炒了你...把他妈的零食给我扔一边去
if you keep monkeying around... Put the fucking snacks away.
我他妈的不想听到你吃零食
I don't wanna fucking hear it!
我们他妈的一直盘旋一小时了
We've been circling for a fucking hour.
告诉他们 我们没油了
Tell them we're running out of gas!
继     承
第 二 季  第６集
好吧 你
Okay, you.
本季度最神奇的时刻到了
It's time for that most magical time of the quarter.
-审计委员会 财务报表  -听起来很棒
- Audit committee. 10-Q. - Sounds amazing.
小西 来吧 给我点暗示 来点暗示
Shiv. Come on. Shadow me, Shadow.
弗兰克 我爸是个骗子 好吧
Frank, my dad's a prick. Come on.
没有...我什么都没有
Nothing... I got nothing.
你知道他答应过我什么
You know what he promised me.
-结果他们都去大会了  -我没办法挤进去
- And they're all up there. - I can't get into that.
怎么 你喜欢这样吗 你喜欢被甩在一边吗
What, you like this? You like being left behind?
西北风神峰会的出席人数有限
There's limited attendance at Argestes.
他们只有一定数量的铂金通行证
They only have a certain amount of platinum passes,
-情况就是这样  -嗯 对
- and that's all there is to it. - Yeah, right.
因为他们没办法制作更多通行证了吗
Because it would be impossible for them to get any more?
因为那样就得找到打印机和墨水 然后...
It'd mean finding printers and ink, and...
难以想象得"复杂" 对吧
Inconceivable, right?
这也是对你的羞辱
This is humiliating for you, too.
来吧 士兵 我们来吧
Come on, soldier. Let's go.
我们检查我们是不是符合通用会计准则的时候
Now, I like to recite Prufrock internally
我喜欢在心里背诵"普鲁弗洛克"[艾略特的诗]
while we check we're GAAP compliant,
不过 你可以随意使用你喜欢的任何方法
but feel free to use whatever method you prefer
-来缓解个中痛苦  -不 去他妈的 我要回家了
- to numb the pain. - No. Fuck this. I'm going home.
-什么...  -我要回家了
- What... - I am going home.
-拜托  - 我有事可做 不
- Come on. - I have shit to do. No.
我要打个关于这个的电话
I'm making a call on this.
你爸爸让我带你看一遍这些文件
Your dad asked me to take you through this stuff.
那 你可以告诉我爸 我自己做的决定 好吗
Well, you can tell my dad I made a decision. Okay?
是游轮事件
It's Cruises.
你好
Hi.
不 我不能发言 抱歉
No, I can't talk, sorry.
我没时间了
Time is what I'm indicating here.
罗伊先生
Mr. Roy.
-欢迎回到西北风神峰会  -谢谢
- Welcome back to Argestes. - Thank you.
-罗伊先生...  -好的
- Mr. Roy... - Yes.
-欢迎回到西北风神峰会  - 谢谢
- Welcome back to Argestes. - Thank you.
节目 以及建议行程
Programs, and suggested itinerary.
行程 很棒
Itinerary, great.
因为我真的希望进入一些...
'Cause I'm really hoping to get into some...
"空客文化徒步" 听起来很让人心碎
"Airbus culture hike", that sounds heart-breaking.
-谢谢  -入住愉快
- Thank you. - Enjoy your stay.
看看你 像雅皮士机械战警一样扫描着每个人的影响力
Look at you scanning for influence like a yuppie Robocop.
那 你打算穿什么参加座谈小组
So, what are you rocking for the panel?
穿夹克还是不穿夹克
Jacket or no jacket?
对 搞得好像我他妈会告诉你一样 老弟
Right, like I'm gonna fuckin' tell you, dude.
-滚开  -好的
- Fuck off. - Okay.
-战略优势  - 很好 不过 给你一个公平的警告
- Strategic advantage. - Fine. But fair warning,
我在考虑到时候不穿袜子
I'm thinking of no socking it.
露出点性感的脚踝
Rockin' some horny ankle cleavage.
怕怕哦
Scary.
-我很害怕  -是的 害怕就对了
- I'm scared. - Yeah, you should be.
或者 我是故意那样说 好吓得你惊慌失措
Or am I just saying that to psych you out?
你好
There.
-先生  -对不起
- Sir. - Excuse me.
-我的小导游 什么事  -嗯 就是...就是...
- My sherpa, what's cookin'? - Yeah, just... just...
刚刚和比尔·盖茨握了手
Might've just touched Bill Gates.
你检查过我要演讲的
Did you check out the acoustics
那个房间的音响了吗
on my room for my talk?
-我...  -你是不是给我报名参加文化徒步
- I... - And did you get me on the culture hike?
我的...我的小木屋里有什么
And what did I... what did I get in my chalet?
是坚果和果盘
Did I get the nut and fruit box
还是香槟和纸镇
or the champagne and paperweight?
坚果
Nuts.
但是...但演讲场地很棒
But... But the talk venue's great.
和罗曼和肯是一个地方
It's the same one as Roman and Ken.
-好的  - 是的 而且...
- Okay. - Yeah. And...
而且不用担心坚果 那个...
And don't worry about the nuts. The...
腰果个头有回旋镖那么大
The cashews are the size of boomerangs.
好的
Okay.
谢谢啦
Thanks.
背心很漂亮 万布斯甘斯 很蓬松啊
Nice vest, Wambsgans. It's so puffy.
谢谢你 罗曼
Thank you, Roman.
里面塞的是什么 你的希望和梦想吗
What's it stuffed with, your hopes and dreams?
登山靴啊 还是全新的呢
Hiking boots. They're pristine.
他来了
Here we go.
好吧 全体起立 欢迎大鸡巴教皇
All right. All rise for Pope Big Dick.
你好 瑞亚
Hello, Rhea.
罗伊先生
Mr. Roy.
你知道我需要什么
You know what I need.
你好
There.
嗯 我只是想说 我不知道
Yeah, just to say, I don't know how
你了解多少最新情况 所有那些细节
up to speed you are, with all of the details,
不过 我只是想说 我们都准备好
but, just to say that we're all lined up
听泛美网络的策略声明了
for the ATN strategy announcement.
嗯 还是旧酒
Yeah, same shit.
换了个新瓶而已
Different wrapper.
好吧 我希望我们不用...我们不会用上横幅 但我们...
Well, I hope we're not gonna... We're not gonna go with that, banner, but we...
你知道 我们选定了 "我们在倾听 "
You know, we settled on, "We're listening."
-测试效果很好  - 测试效果凑合
- It tested great. - It tested fine.
帮我个忙
Do me a favor.
那个人是桑迪·弗内斯吗
Is that Sandy Furness?
是的
Yes.
-是的 是他  -好的 继续说话
- Yeah, yeah. - Well, keep talking.
一直说话
Keep talking.
-好的  - 我不想他搭讪
- Yeah. - I don't want a bump in.
-不想此时此刻被他搭讪  -好的
- Not here, not now. - Okay.
毒蛇想找我搭讪
Vipers would love it.
很高兴...我们很荣幸能成为你的聊天对象...
Gladly... We'd be honored to be your talking partners...
所以 基本上 这次演讲是庆祝
So, basically, the talk is a celebration of
把观众的意见放在首位和中心
putting audience input front and center.
希望在最近的事件之后
And hopefully be really inclusive
能真正做到包容和变化
and quite changey after recent events,
因为泛美网络公民本质上是
because ATN Citizen is essentially
非常相似的 但可以选择...
very similar but with the option of...
他看起来...他看起来怎么样
How's he... How's he looking?
他健康吗
Is he healthy?
他看起来...
He looks...
-并不怎么健康  -他看起来有点衰弱
- Not really. - He looks a little enfeebled.
-好的  -我觉得
- Yeah. - I'd say.
我听说...我听说 可能...
I heard... I heard, maybe...
可能是梅毒
maybe syphilis?
什么 真的吗
What? Really?
-有意思  -这绝对是...
- Interesting. - And that's definitely...
现在很少听到有人得梅毒的了
You don't really hear much about syphilis these days.
很多都是...社交网络病
Very much the... The MySpace of STDs.
不好意思 洛根
Excuse me, Logan.
我刚刚和卡罗丽娜谈过
I, just spoke to Karolina.
消息爆出来了
It came through.
他们要求我们回应
They're asking for a response.
去找个房间 但是动作慢点 别发出动静
Get a room. But slow. No ripples.
这算是房间吗
A room?
抱歉 杂志直接联系了游轮
Sorry. The magazine contacted Cruises directly.
-谁在游轮  - 你好
- Who at Cruises? - Hello?
只有佛罗里达的公关人员
Just Florida PR.
很明显 他们觉得 只要他们在食物链下面的位置找
Obviously, they thought they could get someone
就能找到可能会泄露消息的人
who might spew if they went low on the food chain,
但我已经和他们所有人通报过了
but I had 'em all briefed.
他们有些什么料 掌握了多少
What have they got? How much have they got?
我们不清楚
We don't know.
他们所要求的只是对单次事件的回应
All they're requesting is a response on one element.
-卡罗丽娜说我们有两周时间  -是的
- Karolina said we had two weeks. - Yeah.
好吧 我不知道卡罗丽娜是从哪里得到的消息
Well, I don't know where Karolina got that from,
所以 我...我不会这么确定
so, I... I cannot speak to that.
小西正在和我通话 如果可以...
So I have Shiv on the line, if that's...
小西 我们开了免提
Shiv, you're on speaker.
怎么了 他妈的怎么回事
So, what the fuck is going on?
我听说游轮那边有人在揭发我们的大丑闻
I hear there's a big muck-rake piece coming in on Cruises?
-是啊 没错  -那 是什么丑闻
- Yeah, that's right. - So, what's in it?
我们也不是很清楚
We don't know exactly.
对不起 你哪位
I'm sorry, who is this?
雨果·贝克 公园和游轮部门的
Hugo Baker, Senior Vice President Comms
高级副总裁
for Parks and Cruises.
-嗨  - 等一下 爸爸在吗
- Hi. - Wait. Is Dad there?
他知道我正在接听这个电话吗
Does he know I'm on this call?
-我在这  -好的 那
- I'm here. - Okay, so,
再告诉我一下 这...这是怎么发生的
tell me again, how... How did this happen?
嗯 我们前段时间收到一个消息
Well, we had a tip off some time ago.
纽约杂志正在写一篇重要的文章
New York Magazine working on a substantial piece.
他们对我们提出了有限的指控
They're, only giving us limited allegations
并且要求我们回应
and asking for a response.
好的 所以 有一颗炸弹即将爆炸
Okay, so there's a bomb about to go off,
我们知道是他妈关于什么的吗
and do we know what the fuck is in it?
你为什么这样做 爸爸 你为什么把消息掖着藏着
Why do you do this, Dad? Why do you hoard information?
你不知情 才不会伤害到你
What you don't know can't hurt you.
显然 无论这些指控是什么
Obviously, we are confident on our position,
我们对自己的立场很有信心
regardless of the allegations.
而且 文章会在什么时候发布
And, this'll drop when?
好吧 首先是网上 一天半到两天时间
Well, online first, thirty-six to forty-eight hours.
所以 是的 不是两周时间
So, yeah. Not two weeks.
再说一次 我不知道消息是从哪里泄漏的
Again, I've no idea where that came from.
那 这会让皮尔斯的交易告吹 对吧
So, this sinks Pierce, right?
如果你没有在此之前签好协议 那么...
If you don't get that done and signed off before this drops, then...
我们可以直接封杀吗
Can we kill it?
不 封杀不了 钥匙
No, you can't kill it. Key.
更严重的我都封杀过
I've killed bigger.
不 过去五年发生的丑闻封杀不了
No, not in the last five years.
尊重地说 小西 休息一下 你是新手 好吗
Respectfully, Shiv, take a beat. You're new to this, yeah?
是的 谢谢你他妈的 我就是新手
Yeah, and thank fuck for you I am.
你真是满口都是陈腐苍白的臭气
This stinks of stale, pale male,
你需要一个局外人来给点建议
and you need an outsider to advise.
-勒令停止 对吧  - 是的 雨果 我们正在谈这个
- Cease and desist, right? - Yes, Hugo. We're on that.
不 我们封杀他们 不管他们有多少猛料
No, we go, how deep are their pockets,
我们他妈的吓死他们
fuckin' scare the shit out of them.
是的 放话出去
Yeah, get word around,
说我们的律师会竭尽全力
our lawyers will go balls to the wall,
说他超级生气
say he's super pissed.
潜台词是这是在针对我们 我们感觉他们在报复我们
Subtext is this is personal, we're feeling vindictive,
让高层管理人员问问他们 如果我们搞到他们破产的话
get the senior management asking where they'll go
-他们会落到什么下场  - 爸爸 勒令停止
- if we bankrupt them. - Dad, cease and desist
和火力全开的反常举动有非常高的风险
and a full-on shit-flinging freak-out is very high risk,
但是我们可以让他们延期发布
but we could get them to delay.
告诉他们 我们会和他们一起研究
Tell them we'll get into it all with them,
我们会合作 全力以赴 然后让这篇报道胎死腹中
we'll cooperate, play it all out, - and then stiff them. -
我们能提供更多的条件换取延期发布吗
We could offer up morsels in exchange for postponement?
我们或许可以找到点蛛丝马迹
We might be able to find something,
-也许在演播室之外  - 不
- maybe out of the studios? - No.
条件得非常优厚
Bigger. Juicier.
那些人...抱歉
People who are... Sorry.
妈的 抱歉
Fuck, I'm sorry.
正在写游轮虐待丑闻的人
People who are writing about cruise abuse scandals
不会因为写得像"兄弟会男孩2"那样情节曲折
are not gonna be getting all kissy for a plot twist
-就受到所有人欢迎  -不 延期发布太软弱了
- on frat baby two. - No. Delay is too soft.
爸爸 别理他 加快交易进度
Dad, ignore him. Accelerate the deal.
那你他妈以为我们一直在干什么 西沃恩
What the fuck do you think we've been doing, Siobhan?
嗯 我他妈完全不知道 爸爸
Well, I have no fuckin' idea, Dad,
因为你从不告诉我任何事情
because you never tell me anything.
全盘让步
Cave on everything,
让他们在丑闻败露之前 至少签署
get them to at least sign a letter of intent
一份意向书 应该能熬过签协议
before the story breaks, it should hold.
不 爸 我们正面面对他们 我们吓唬他们
No, Dad, we go for the piece, we scare them into thinking
让他们去顾虑自己的境况岌岌可危
what they have isn't solid,
我们直接他妈的杀 杀 杀
just fuckin' kill, kill, kill.
肯 你来负责
Ken, you're on that.
开始散布我他妈有多么不讲道理的消息
Start sprinkling how fucking unreasonable I am,
格丽 加速交易进度 如果有必要就签署正式收购意向书
Gerri, foot down on the deal. LOI if we need,
他们已经箭在弦上 我们他妈的在文章发布之前
they're half-pregnant. Let's finish the fucking job
-完成这笔交易  -当然 但我不得不说
- before this breaks. - Sure, but I have to say
-法律上来说...  -现在就办
- just legally... - Now.
我现在就要
I need it now.
今年的流动资金有多少
What money's floating this year?
你是说可以救急的吗
You mean for a white knight?
我可以让罗曼试试能探到多少资金
I could see what Roman could scratch up.
-汤姆呢  - 罗曼更饥渴
- Tom? - Roman's hungry.
好吧 小西 你到这里来吧
All right. Shiv, let's get you out here.
-我在媒体方面需要你帮忙  -你说什么
- I need your help on the optics. - Excuse me?
不 我...我才不以这样的身份
No. I... I am not flying out to Argestes
来西北风神峰会呢
to be the face of this.
那么你他妈的打电话干什么 西沃恩
Then what the fuck are you doing on the phone, Siobhan?
那 欢迎大家
So, welcome everyone,
参加空中客车的文化与领导力徒步
to the Airbus Cultural and Leadership Walk.
我们今天聚集在这里
We're gathered here today with a commitment
承诺可持续发展和管理
to sustainability and stewardship.
因此 今天这个基于地方的学习将重点关注
So, this place-based learning today will focus on
为你创造机会 获得...
creating opportunities for you to gain the...
- 嘘...汤姆  -视角...
- Sh... Tom! - Perspective for...
对不起 汤姆
Sorry, Tom?
汤姆
Tom!
-伙计  -出问题了
- Buddy. - Problem.
你没接电话
You're not picking up?
-伙计 这是一个伟大的团体  -对不起
- Dude, this is a great group. - Sorry.
你做得不错
You did good.
我就像掉进了一桶等着被卖的山雀里面一样
It's like I've fallen into a barrel of deal tits.
是啊 那...那 关于你的演讲 有一个问题
Yeah. So... So, there's a thing about your talk.
我的演讲
My talk?
是的....等你上台演讲的时候
Yes.... When it got circulated,
法律部和市场沟通部希望你能够知道
legal and comms wanted you to be aware that
也许我们不应该用"泛美网络 我们在倾听 "
maybe we shouldn't go with "ATN: We're listening."
好的 我的意思是 我真的喜欢 "我们在倾听 "
Okay. I mean, I really do like, "We're listening."
这听起来像...我的意思是 听起来我们真的在倾听
It sounds like... I mean, it sounds like we're listening.
-不 当然 它只是...  -是的
- No. Sure, it's just... - Yeah.
只是 显然 在机顶盒上的
It's just, there's apparently, in the EPG
电子节目菜单里
on the set top boxes,
语音激活模式 就...
the voice activation mode, it does...
就是说 我们的数据收集方面有一个灰色区域
Like, there's a gray area in terms of our data collection,
所以 我们有点像是
so that we are kind of like,
我们其实真的在"倾听"[偷听]
We actually are listening.
我们在偷听吗
We're listening?
这很复杂 但是...但是 是的
It's complicated, but... but, yeah.
似乎我们有时候
It seems that we are sometimes,
倾听地非常积极
listening quite aggressively.
-我们真的在偷听吗  -是的
- We're listening? - Yeah.
但这只是为了最大化用户体验
But it's just to, like, maximize the user experience.
但是 如果这个消息泄露出去
But if that was to break,
-也许...  -我操
- maybe... - Fuck!
是的
So, yeah.
所以 问题是 由你来说这话是不是明智
So, the question is, is it a smart thing for you to be saying,
你说"我们在倾听"
"We're listening",
而我们是真的在偷听
when we are indeed listening?
为什么我不知道这事
Why was I not aware of this?
那家伙说 这基本上是合法的
Well, it's basically legal, the guy said.
但他不想把这话放在电子邮件里
But he didn't wanna put that in an email,
-所以...  -那我现在要怎么说
- so... - What am I gonna call it now?
我不知道 也许...
I don't know. Maybe...
他们建议用"我们听到了你的声音 "那样好点吗
They suggested "we hear you." Is that any better?
我们测试过这句 格雷格 该死的
We tested this, Greg! God damn!
-是的 我很乐意 是啊  -太棒了
- Yeah, I'd love to. Yeah, yeah. - Great.
一切都好吗
Everything is okay?
玛西娅
Marcia.
最近可能会爆一些事情出来
It's possible that some things will come out.
恶心的事情
Nasty things.
大家会对我 对公司说三道四
People will say things about me, about the company.
我需要知道你和我在一起
I might need to know you're with me.
洛根...
Logan...
当我和某人在一起时 我就是和他在一起
when I am with someone, I am with them.
看着我
Look at me.
我知道你是什么样的人
I know who you are.
罗曼
Rome.
你看到那个人了吗
You see that guy?
阿斯加洛夫
Asgarov.
爱德华 他吗
Eduard. Him?
你爸爸对打探到巨额资本很感兴趣
Your dad is intrigued by sounding out big money,
如果皮尔斯交易失败的话
in the event that the Pierce deal goes under.
嗯 这个交易不是已经木已成舟了吗
Well, it's a done deal though, right?
嗯 我也不知道
Yeah, I don't know.
你能先找他聊聊吗
Could you start a conversation
以免我们需要紧急备用方案
in case we need an emergency exit?
救急资金 私有化
White knight, go private?
和爱德华谈吗
With Eduard?
穿着不知道什么皮做的懒汉鞋...我不知道
In his loafers made from the skin of... I don't know,
那是什么 人权活动家吗
what is that? Human rights activists?
他老爸在中央银行有巨额资金流
His dad has a hose attached to the central bank.
显然 他正在构思一个300年投资期限的概念
He's apparently conceptualising a 300-year investing horizon.
那 这算什么 补偿炮吗
So, this is what, make-up sex?
这是你向我负荆请罪
This is you grinding yourself against me
因为没有告诉我关于小西和我爸的事的道歉方式吗
and saying sorry for not telling me about Shiv and Dad?
罗曼 你爸爸想让汤姆去办这事 我推荐了你
Roman, your dad wanted Tom on this. I said you.
好了 拜托
Come on, please.
我不知道36小时后情况会变成什么样子
I don't know what the world is gonna look like in 36 hours.
只是...尽你所能
Just... Just do what you can.
我不知道被别人看见我们说话是不是明智
I don't know if it's wise for us to be seen talking.
我也可以拉拉家常的
I can take a bit of tittle tattle.
嗯 你是一只老犀牛
Well, you're an old rhino.
我只是一只轻浮的小麻雀
I'm just a flighty, little sparrow.
我们想明天在这里签约
We'd like to ink it here tomorrow.
当然...我的意思是
Sure... I mean,
我明白你这边需要权宜之计
we appreciate the need for expediency from your end.
据我所知 我们离最终敲定还有一段距离
From what I understand, we're still some distance apart.
分手费吗
The break fee?
告诉你们的人 如果他们施压 我们会让步的
Tell your crowd if they push, we'll cave.
削弱你自己的地位吗
Undermining your own position?
你能起诉自己吗
Could you sue yourself?
听着 瑞亚
Listen, Rhea.
你能不能说服她 如果她明天不在这里签约
Can you persuade her that if she doesn't sign here tomorrow,
我们可能会放弃交易
we might walk?
晚点....
Later....
我听说文化徒步是热门项目
I hear the culture hike's the hot ticket.
但我不确定你对文化或徒步有任何兴趣
But I'm not sure you're crazy about either one of those things.
-为了明天的事  -那 上午11点
- For tomorrow? - So, 11:00 AM,
我们有托马斯·费舍尔的"不平等的品质"
we've got Thomas Fisher doing "Qualities of Inequality".
-有什么不同...  -对
- What difference... - Right.
看看是谁来了啊
Look who it is.
爸爸的乖宝宝
Daddy's boy.
我听说你们的员工现在都在自杀
I hear your staff are all killing themselves now.
是的 因为他们考虑到你可能会做他们的老板
Yeah, at the thought that you could be their boss.
而你永远也做不成
Which you never will be.
不 当然 因为你们这些人
No, sure, because of all the acquisitions
正在奔走的收购交易 真的让自己膨胀起来了吗
you guys are making, like, really bloating yourselves up?
这里有一份75块的科布沙拉
There's a 75-dollar Cobb salad here.
伙计 你应该把它买了 用它作为防御
Dude, you should buy that, use that as a defense.
是啊 是的 也许吧
Yeah. Yeah, maybe.
不是科布沙拉 就是其他美味的东西
Either the Cobb salad or something else tasty.
那...很吓人啊 会是什么呢
That's... scary. What could that be?
是个汉堡包吗 是鱿鱼吗
Is it a hamburger? Is it calamari?
是他妈的...伙计 是纳普斯特公司吗
Is it fuckin'... Dude, is it Napster?
听着 我只是想说 老实说
Look, I'm just gonna say, honestly,
我们有交易在进行
we have something coming in,
这会让你的收购难以持续下去 所以...
and it's gonna make your deal untenable. So...
我想 作为朋友 我应该提一下
I thought, as a friend, I should mention it.
真是好心啊
That's kind.
就像"永远最好的朋友"一样
That's like BFF shit right there.
听着 我不是在和你胡扯 斯图
Look, I'm not fuckin' with you, Stew.
我用我孩子的生命发誓
I swear on my children's lives
现在 我们有一个十拿九稳的交易
that right now, we have a deal in the bag
天量的规模 大到毁了你的收购计划 好吗
so big that it's gonna kill your approach. Okay?
而且 我对于我们之间
And I feel a certain level of regret
友谊的发展 感到一定的遗憾
about how things have panned out between us.
事实上 小肯 恕我直言...
The thing is, Ken, and due respect...
我真的不相信你
I really don't trust you.
所以...等等一下 所以...
So... So, wait a second. So...
所以 我们要用 我们...
So, we're gonna go with, we...
我们要用 "我们听到了你的声音"
We're gonna go with, "we hear you"?
"我们听到了你的声音" 是啊
"We hear you". Yeah.
你还在担心吗
Are you still worried?
"我们在倾听" "我们听到了你的声音"
"We're listening", "We hear you"?
这是同样的问题 不是吗
It's the same problem, isn't it?
好吧 可能后面这句没那么明显
Well, it's maybe less active.
你知道 它...更...不能...
You know, it's... it's more... Couldn't...
"我忍不住瞥见你换衣服 除非
"Couldn't help glimpse you changing unless,
我们在你的浴室里放一个偷窥摄像头 "
we put a spy cam in your shower."
"我们听到了你的声音"
"We hear you".
我认为这是个问题 我认为这是个问题
I think it's a problem. I think it's a problem.
我们...我们在倾听 我们听到了你的声音
We're... we're listening, we're hearing you.
我认为这话应该是"我们在听" 但是...
I think it needs to be like, "We're hearing," but...
但是 听上去没什么感觉
but nothing that's gonna bite me in the ass.
好的
Yeah, okay.
-你懂吗  - 所以也许应该是 泛美网络
- You know? - So maybe it's like, ATN
我们在这里陪着你" 把"这里"拼写成倾听
We're here for you", and "here" spelled H-E-A-R.
"我们为你倾听" 什么乱七八糟的
"We're hear for you"? That's just jibberish.
"我们为你倾听"
"We hear for you"!
好的  "我们为你倾听" 不错
Okay. "We hear for you." Yeah.
那这听上去就像是 "我们...我们...我们为你倾听
So that might be like, "We... We... We hear for you,
伙计 因为你不需要倾听 我们听到了"
man, 'cause you don't need to hear. We hear."
-是的 我们...  -还有...还有
- Yeah, we... - And also... also,
"我们在这里陪你" 对吧 这...
"we're here for you." Right? Is that...?
-是的"我们是你的人"  -我说的有道理吗
- Yeah. "We're your guys." - Am I making sense?
这很好 因为这就像是 并不清楚到底是什么意思
It's good, because it's like, it's not clear exactly what the hell it means,
-所以 很多诠释空间  -是的
- so, lots of wiggle-room. - Yes.
-"我们为你倾听"  -"我们为你倾听"
- "We hear for you." - "We hear for you."
-是的  -好的
- Yeah. - Okay.
-好了 我是万布斯甘斯  -"我们为你倾听"
- Okay. Wamsgans. - "We hear for you."
对不起 爱德华 不好意思 我不是想显得粗鲁
Excuse me, Eduard. Sorry, don't mean to be rude.
我是罗曼·罗伊
I'm, Roman Roy.
-伙计  -你好吗
- Man. - How you doin'?
你觉得我们可以聊聊吗
Do you think we can talk for a minute?
抱歉 谢谢
Sorry. Thanks.
那 你怎么样...
So, how you doin' with...
你懂的 就到处走走 四处搞搞
You know, just walking around, getting pitched to fuck.
是啊
Yeah.
我听说你们有麻烦了
I hear you're in trouble.
代理权吗
The proxy?
不 我的意思是 我们有压力
No. I mean, we're under pressure,
但是 是的 我们没什么好担心的
but, yeah, nothing we're worried about.
-谢谢  -对 那...
- Thanks. - Right. So...
你跟我联系 是想打我那一大袋赃款的主意吗
you wanna hit me up for my big bag of swag?
波拉特的操蛋的输油管这类玩意吗
Borat the fucking pipeline piece of shit?
不 拜托 伙计 你是个很有眼光的人
No. Come on, man. You're a discerning fellow
每个人都...你知道...你跟我开玩笑吗
that everyone, like... You know... Are you kidding me?
你就像他妈的沃霍尔 你知道...
You're like fucking Warhol of, you know...
- 的...  -的什么
- of... - Of?
-的 你知道我从哪里来的吗  -斯坦福吗
- Of? You know where I'm from? - Stanford?
我的意思是 哪里人...不 我不知道
I mean, Originally... No, I don't.
我不知道你从哪里来的
I do not know where you come from,
不过 你知道吗
and you know what?
我很尴尬 我很乐意知道
I'm embarrassed about it. I would like to know.
伙计 巴库[阿塞拜疆共和国首都]天天都在发生烂事...
Man, the shit happening in Baku...
我说真的
I'm serious.
你在嘲笑我们吗 我们在嘲笑你们
You're laughing at us? We're laughing at you.
你给我带来了什么
What is it you're, bringing to me?
除了乞讨碗以外
Other than a begging bowl?
我没有乞讨碗 只是 你知道
No begging bowl here. Just, you know,
为你提供一些 可能的 投资 机会
offering you some, maybe, investment, opportunities.
你他妈的是个新闻人 对吧
You're a fucking news guy, right?
-是的  -为什么新闻这么...
- Yeah. - Why is the news so...
-你懂我意思吗  -是的
- You know? - Yes.
-不 我知道...我知道  -是的
- No, I know... I know. - Yeah.
这非常...是的 我不知道为什么新闻是这个样子
It's very... Yeah. I don't know why the news is like that.
-我讨厌那样  -我们可以谈谈这个
- I hate that. - We can talk about that.
当然 绝对
Sure. Absolutely.
是的 带有积极议程的新闻
Yeah, the news with a positive agenda.
我所在地区的积极议程
A positive agenda for my region.
好的
Okay.
但是独立 我们愿意资助真实的故事 但不要插手
But independent. Real stories we'd fund, but hands off.
-对  -客观的
- Right. - Objective.
百分百独立的 可以吗
A hundred percent independent?
但是 是从我们的角度来看
But from our point of view.
好吧 是啊 这是一个非常非常诱人的项目 是的
All right. Yeah. That's a really, really enticing project, yeah.
我愿意继续谈谈这个
I'd like to keep the conversation going.
-太棒了很高兴和你聊天  -嗯
- Great. Good talking to you. - Yeah.
抱歉 铁粉一个...
Sorry. Big fan...
崇拜...崇拜你所有的钱
of... of all your money.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是怎么回事
What's going on?
你...你在吸古柯碱吗
You... You doin' the old cocaine?
我能要...可以给我一道吗
Could I get... Maybe get a little bump?
一道 格雷格 怎么回事
Bump? Greg, what happened?
外面就像个权力派对
It's like a power party out there.
有 科技巨头 像超模 还有...
Like, tech titans and, like, supermodels, and...
我只是需要一点点激励
I just need a little boost.
好的 好吧 祝你好运
Okay. Well, good luck with that.
-伙计 拜托 拜托 停手  -不
- Dude, come on. Come on. Stop. - No.
他们没有纸巾 都变成了绿色的狗屎
They don't have paper towels. They've gone all green and shit.
伙计 你来真的吗
Dude, seriously?
所以 突然之间 我发现自己在负责十亿美元的预算
So, all of a sudden, I find myself in charge of like a billion-dollar budget,
这真的令人兴奋 而且...这...
and it's really exciting. And it's... And it's...
我以为我会...我以为我会...
I thought I would... I thought I would...
你知道 我以为自己会感到压力
You know, I would suffer from the pressure,
但我他妈的喜欢这样 我很喜欢
but I fucking love it. I really love it.
天哪 小西 你怎么来了
My God. Shiv! What the fuck?
-我也很高兴见到你 汤姆  -很高兴见到你
- Nice to see you too, Tom. - Nice to see you.
怎么...你为什么不告诉我你要来
How are... Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
临时决定的事情
It was a last-minute thing.
-嗨 小西·罗伊  -很高兴认识 我叫妮娅
- Hi. Shiv Roy. - Pleasure. Nia.
当然 是的 祝贺你们成功上市
Of course. Yeah, congratulations on the IPO.
-谢谢  -你方便...
- Thank you. - Would you just...
-你能给我们一点时间吗  -当然
- Could you give us a moment? - Yeah.
-回头见  -再见
- See you later? - See ya.
你来了
But you're here.
-希望这样没有造成你的不便  -不 不
- Hope that's not inconvenient. - No! No.
不 我不是在...不 这...很好
No, I'm not being... No. It... It's nice.
你来了 只是...你知道 你经常...
This. It's just... You know, you're often...
这令人不安 我的意思是 我们一直发信息
It's unsettling. I mean, the texts.
对 对不起 只是...我一直很忙
Yeah, sorry. It's... I've just been busy.
随便聊
Whatever.
有一个潜在的危机即将来临...
There's a potential crisis coming....
有一位记者正在调查游轮
There's a journalist looking into cruises,
并且有一篇重要文章即将发表
and there's a big piece coming.
好的
Okay.
-什么内容  -我们也不清楚
- What? - We don't know exactly.
-过来  -妈的
- Come here. - Shit.
他们...他们要拿我当替罪羊吗 这篇文章是关于我的吗
Are... Are they scapegoating me? Is the piece about me?
不 这篇文章还没发表
No, the piece hasn't come out yet.
-没有人读过这篇文章  -这篇文章是关于...不 好的
- No one's read the piece. - Is this about... No. Okay.
什么都没发生 不 我们正在围堵
Nothing has happened. No, we're jamming it up.
我只是把我知道的告诉你 好吗
I'm just telling you what I know, okay?
好的 我脸红了吗 我感觉我脸变红了
Okay. Have I gone red? I feel like I'm going red.
突然间每个人都想要我来这里
Suddenly everyone wants me here.
-格丽打来电话 瑞亚打来电话  -是吧 瑞亚
- Gerri called. And Rhea called. - Right. Rhea?
是啊 突然之间 我成了每个人最喜欢的防爆工具
Yeah. Suddenly I'm everyone's favorite piece of blast protection.
-对  -嗯
- Right. - Yeah.
-防弹山雀或别的什么东西  -那...那他们...
- Bullet-proof tits or something. - So... So what...
他们想引用谁的话 他们找我了吗
What do they want a quote on? Did they ask for me?
汤姆 这篇文章不是关于你的
Tom, the piece is not about you.
但是有一条线索...有一条线索 可以从老莫追踪到比尔
But there's a trail from... There's a trail from Mo
再追踪到我 你是安全的
to Bill to me. You're safe.
-这样很好 但是...  -是的
- Which is good, but... - Yeah.
我在局外 我什么都不知道
I'm on the outside. I don't know anything.
-所以我才很有用  -是的
- That's why I'm useful. - Yeah.
好的
Okay.
你是打算睡妮娅·贝顿吗
Were you trying to bang Nia Bayton?
你说什么
Excuse me?
没有
Nothing.
不 老天 没有
Well, no. God! No.
-小西  -好吧 没事
- Shiv. - Right. Fine.
小西
Shiv.
我的意思是 我没有这想法 但如果我有...
I mean, I wasn't. But if I was...
根据我们的约定 实际上我可以这样
that would actually be, under the arrangement, okay.
对吧
You know?
-汤姆 我认识她  -嗯 你听说过她 但...
- Tom. I know her. - Well, you know of her, but...
这他妈的会有点尴尬
It would be a bit fucking awkward.
用用你的常识 好吗
Just use your common sense, okay?
对 因为我可能会说 你知道
Right, 'cause I might say that, you know,
和一个你哥哥资助的
spending the night with an actor
戏剧里演员一起过夜
in a play financed by your brother
而且十天都没有告诉我 这有点...尴尬
and not telling me for ten days was a little bit... awkward.
拜托 妮娅是个真实的人
Come on. Nia's a real person.
有真实的脸
With a face.
好吧
Fine.
不
No.
好的
Okay.
总之 无论如何 你来了 真好
So, anyway. It's nice that you're here.
嗯 我想你了
Yeah, I missed you.
进展如何
How'd it go?
他可能有无数的钱
He might be good for infinite billions,
但是 他想要一个前线新闻频道来宣传
but he wants a front news channel to spew propaganda.
-这样可以吗  -应该可以吧
- We into that? - I guess.
-取决于金额  -对
- Depends on the numbers. - Right.
另外 整个...我的意思是...
Plus, the whole... I mean...
显然 这是个道德的雷区
Obviously, it's an ethical minefield.
当然 当然
Sure. Of course.
但是 如果我们采取"管他妈的"立场
But if we took a position of "fuck it"?
嗯 这个道德立场很有意思
Well, that's an interesting ethical position.
那弃了吗
Silo it off?
话说 这是为什么 为什么他让我试探这个
Well, what is it? Why's he got me chasing this?
他还没有告诉你吗
He still hasn't told you?
很可悲 不是吗
Pathetic, isn't it?
-我不知道 我不能说  -对 当然
- I don't know. I can't say. - Right. Course.
当然不能
Course not.
你知道吗 现在 如果你知道...
You know, right now, if, you know...
如果他发生任何不测 你就是书面钦定的
If anything happens to him, you're on the piece of paper
王国的下一任统治者
as the next ruler of the kingdom.
我想 我自己非常清楚发生这种情况的几率有多大
I think I've been made well aware of how unlikely it is that will transpire.
当然 对 但是 你知道吗 你工作上...
Sure. Right. But you know how you're...
非常高效 且很擅长
so efficient and good at your job?
-好的 谢谢  -但也有点
- Well, thank you. - But also sort of, like,
不显眼 就像壁纸一样 有点...
invisible? Like wallpaper, like a...
无聊 陈旧
boring old sort of nothing.
就像一个称职的聪明的文件柜
Like a competent kind of clever filing cabinet
每一个拥有你的人似乎都会很满足
that everyone seems content to have around?
-而我就像一个他妈的摇滚明星蠢蛋  -对
- And I'm like a fucking - rockstar moron. - Right.
我的意思是 显然 这些是我们的公众形象
I mean, obviously, these are our public profiles,
不是我们的真正本质
not our true essences.
我有想法 不过 你继续说
I have thoughts, but continue.
好吧 只是灵光一闪 比如 有没有可能
Well, just floating, like, is there an angle here,
我们组队
for a team up?
比如 我 充当泰山的角色
Like, me, kind of a Jagger-Tarzan,
面向前方 穿过树林
fronting things up and swinging through trees
带着我的小鸡鸡 唱着歌大杀四方
with my little dick, singing and killing shit,
而你 等我回到家里 在家里给我们煮汤
and you, back home, cooking us soup,
并且确保财务上正确无误
and making sure the numbers are right.
摇滚明星和鼹鼠女人
Rockstar and the mole woman?
你真的是在向我推销你自己
You're really selling me.
但是 我们会是董事长和总裁的搭配
But it would be chair and CEO.
或者总裁和董事长
Or CEO and chair.
而你会有钱到这个地步 "操你妈的
And you will get properly "fuck you,
操你妈的 我根本不关心气候变化
fuck you, I don't even care about climate change,
我在新西兰和我的私人军队在一起呢"
I'm in New Zealand with my own private army" rich.
而不是可怜的在葡萄园里有一栋
Not like some pathetic asshole beach house
海滨别墅那样的穷逼
on the Vineyard rich.
很晚了
It's late.
你走吧
Off you go.
谢谢 鼹鼠女人
Thanks, mole woman.
谢谢 摇滚明星
Thanks, rockstar.
晚安
Night night.
老天 我来了
God. Here I am.
他会让我脱掉鞋子检查吗
Is he gonna make me take off my shoes?
-你睡得好吗  -睡了几个小时 跟往常一样
- You slept okay? - Couple of hours. The usual.
我应该拿它干嘛呢
What am I supposed to do with this?
-戴着它 南希  -绝不
- You wear it, Nancy. - Absolutely not.
好了 一起乐一乐吧
Come on. Join the fun.
虚假谦逊的秀场 每个人都戴了一个
A show of false humility. Everyone wears one.
扎克伯格也戴了一个
Zuckerberg wears one.
给我一支笔 我会在我的脸上写下我的名字
Hand me a pen and I'll write my name across my face.
你还好吗
You okay for this?
我觉得我的立场表达得非常明确
I think I made my position perfectly clear,
但是 不知道出于什么原因 你觉得我迫切需要
but for whatever reason you felt it urgently necessary
放下正在喝的西柚汁和正在吃的煎蛋
to put me in transit for grapefruit juice
-赶到这里来  -你应该按照自己的节奏来
- and a plate of eggs. - You should go at your own pace,
绝对没错 这很有必要
absolutely, that's imperative.
只不过我觉得 这笔交易对你来说太划算了
I just think this is such a good deal for you.
对...对我们来说
For... For us.
这一点点急促很值得
That it's worth a little haste.
那 我们准备了一个小房间用来签约
So, we have a little room for signing right in there.
只是进去签了就完了 你还好吗
Just in and out, and boom. You okay?
是海拔的影响吗
Is it the altitude?
我不知道 也许吧 是什么...什么...
I don't know. Maybe. What... what's...
-是什么...  -是的 我们...
- What's with the...? - Yeah, let's...
-我们换张桌子吧  -不 不 不用
- Let's move you around. - No, no. No.
我他妈又不是自己不能动 你不...
I'm not in a fucking wheelchair. You don't...
我很好 我没事
I'm good. I'm good.
-墨镜  -是的
- Sunglasses. - Yeah.
我刚接到卡罗丽娜的电话
I just had a call from Karolina.
杂志社不合作
The magazine is not cooperating.
他们感觉被欺负了 这篇文章可能会提前到
They feel bullied, and the piece might go up
今天早上上网 纸媒周一发表
this morning. Print, Monday.
操 操 操
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
嗯...什么时候 我们还有多少时间
Well... When? How long do we have?
几小时 也许几分钟 我...
Hours. Maybe minutes. I...
我们怎么办 我们取消签约吗
What do we do? Do we bail?
爸
Dad?
我在想
I'm thinking.
我们应该离开 我们需要离开这里
We should leave. We need to get out of here.
我们走吧 我们去..
Let's leave. We go..
道个歉
Apologies.
好吧 我觉得自己像舞会上的美女
Well, I feel like the belle of the ball out here.
非常谨慎的位置
Very discreet.
你对这张桌子满意吗 四面八方都可以看到
You're happy with this table? Visible enough from all sides?
这一切都很青春期 不是吗
It's all quite adolescent, isn't it?
那 我们准备签约了 对吧
So, we're there. Correct?
对分手费很满意吧 其他方面呢
Happy about the break fee, the rest?
对不起 我错过前言了吗 我听说今天是
Sorry, did I miss the preamble? I heard that you were
因为你打算为自己在特恩海文发脾气的事情道歉
going to apologise for your outburst at Ternhaven.
我...我...抱歉 我累了
I... I... Sorry. I'm tired.
嗯 这值得赞赏
Well, that's appreciated.
我爸只是在反映
My dad is just reflecting our desire
我们希望尽快 友好地
to get this concluded as swiftly
-达成协议的愿望  -是的
- and amicably as possible. - Yes.
每天都发一封邮件 开一个会 打一个电话
Every day a letter, a meeting, a call.
恐怕我的新陈代谢有点慢
I'm afraid my metabolism tends a little slower.
今天下午晚些时候 我们要和表亲们汇报下最新情况
We're due a check-in with the cousins later on this afternoon.
是的 但我们可以签约
Yeah, but we can sign.
我们准备签字了
We are ready to sign.
-肯  -是的 就在那边
- Ken? - Yeah. Right in there.
我们想着可以先签字 然后在这里享用美味的早餐
We thought we could sign and then have a nice breakfast - out here.
不过 我们签约之前 我...
But before we do, I...
我觉得 也许我们可以先在这里展开更广泛的讨论
I think there's perhaps a wider conversation to be had here.
我们有兴趣探讨这个选项...对不起 我...
We would be interested in exploring the option... I'm sorry. I...
点了餐我才能集中注意力
I can't concentrate until I order.
我的天啦 真贵
Good God, the prices.
纽约客
迷失在大海:
在韦斯达·罗伊科集团
蔓延着
凌辱与掩盖的文化
给我 给我一杯饮用水就好了 谢谢
I'll. I'll just have tap water, thank you.
不 不用了 谢谢
No, no, thank you.
我们有兴趣探讨这个选项
We would be interested in exploring the option
基于PGM集团绩效的奖金
of a bonus based on PGM performance.
当然 我们可以承担法律费用
Of course. We could cover the legal fees.
你那边的 以及外聘的律师费用
Your side, outside counsel.
全部我们承担
The whole thing.
嗯 这...这真的不是我们在这里要讨论的
Well, this... this isn't really for us to discuss here, surely.
好吧 我想我已经解释过了 我们的耐心是有限的
Well, I think I've explained, there's a limit to our patience.
洛根 我想除了西瓜
Logan, I think perhaps we're not going to agree
我们不会达成任何协议
to anything over watermelon.
嗯 那会带来什么代价
Well, what's it gonna take?
为什么我们还在绕圈子
Why are we still fuckin' around?
我想 也许我们都需要
I think perhaps we all need
少点平铺直叙
a little less sunshine and vinegar.
最后总会有点急躁 我们没事的
It always gets a little testy at the end. We're all good.
南 我们能不能至少签署一份正式收购意向书
Nan, is there not a way we could sign the LOI at least?
爸爸 我在想
Dad, I'm wondering if
也许我们应该去下一个约会了
maybe we should get to our next appointment?
当然 好的 当然
Yeah, sure. Sure.
你们去赴约吧 让我们先咀嚼一会儿
Why don't you do that? Let us chew a while.
-回见  -回头见
- Soon. - See you later.
那 你们怎么看
So, what do we think?
很糟糕 但不是...我不知道
It's bad, but not... I don't know.
我们本来应该给他们施加更大压力的
We should have gone at them harder.
给我纸质文本 现在
Paper copy. Now.
两分钟后从接待处送过来
Coming up from reception in two.
那全世界除了我之外 其余他妈的所有人都能读到了 是吧
So everyone in the fuckin' world has read it except me?
好吧 链接在哪里 为什么没有人给我发链接
Okay, so where's the link? Why did no one send me the link?
你他妈自己搜索就行了
Just fucking Google it.
搜索什么 我不知道我们干了些什么
Google what? I don't know what we did.
"明亮的星 云霄飞车 强奸"
"Brightstar roller coaster rape."
-给我点关键词  -现在给你发链接
- Give me something. - Sending link now.
谢谢
Thank you.
妈的 我操
Well, fuck me.
你觉得他们还能把这些字打印得再小点儿吗
Do you think they could make this text any fucking smaller?
这写得太阴郁了
This is pretty gray.
不过 也很生动
Yeah, but also vivid.
吓唬他们这事干得很"棒"啊
Great work on frightening them off.
延迟发布做得也很"好"
Good work on stalling.
我正在阅读
I'm reading.
-感谢你过来  -嗯 当然
- Thanks for coming. - Yeah, sure.
大家都在补习阅读技能吗 来吧
Is everyone here remedial at reading? Come on.
是我自己的问题还是这他妈就是废话 也许这样 也许那样
Is it me or is this bullshit? Maybe this, maybe that.
-罗曼 说话小心点  -这是不是就是那种事情
- Rome, careful. - Is this one of those things
我需要女人来向我解释为什么这样不好的那种
that I need a woman to explain to me why it's bad?
-小西 这很糟吗  -别他妈问我
- Shiv? Is it bad? - Don't fuckin' ask me.
我又不是你的盖革计数器[用于测量放射性]
I'm not your grope Geiger counter.
你怎么看 罗曼
What do you think, Rome?
我觉得糟糕 但不是非常糟糕
I do think it's bad, but it's not that fuckin' bad.
他妈的
Fuck.
谁爆料的
What's the protein?
他们找到了一个女的 凯尔森
They found a woman, Keerson.
她在90年代中期的时候在游轮上工作
She was working the cruises back in the mid '90s,
在公开场合用的名字是 莱斯特·麦克林托克
name-checks Lester McClintock.
她说 莫叔叔要求与她和其他舞蹈演员发生性关系
She says Uncle Mo asked for sex with her and the other dancers
这样才和她们续签合同
to get their contracts renewed.
你们都知道这个事吗
Were all of you in on this?
你们都知道这事会爆出来吗
Did you all know this was coming?
-这不是非常详细  -了不起
- It's not ultra-detailed. - Amazing.
-所以他们上床了  -写的是性剥削
- So they fucked. - It says sexual exploitation.
嗯 她说她是唯一一个
Yeah, she's saying that she was one of the only ones
拒绝签署保密协议的人
who refused to sign an NDA
结果导致她的职业生涯被我们毁了
and that we derailed her career as a result.
-是吗  -不 听着
- Is that it? - No, look.
以前老休森的事情 女人跳海然后淹死了...
The old Hewson story, the woman that jumped and drowned...
如果凯尔森出了什么事呢
what if something happened to her?
这...这只是暗示
It's... It's just innuendo.
那个舞蹈演员说 她听过其他几十个
The dancer says that she heard stories of
签署了保密协议的女人的故事
dozens of other women who actually signed the NDAs.
好的 但是 就实际情况而言呢
Okay, but in terms of actual stuff?
没有太多具体细节 都是些令人毛骨悚然的言辞
There's not a lot of specifics. It's spooky words,
你懂的 数据擦除 保密协议 阴阳日志
you know, data wipes, NDAs, shadow logs,
遮掩游轮的玩忽职守
hiding cruise malpractice.
不过 事实很冷酷 这只是一位20世纪90年代的女性
But cold hard facts, it's one woman in the 1990s,
而不是四年前的20位女性
not like 20 women four years ago.
很好 我很高兴我们能够在受害者加减法这方面算的这么好
Great. I'm glad we're able to do such good victim math.
格丽只是说 这件事不一定会成为导火线
Gerri's just saying it doesn't necessarily - punch through.
当然 但是 你知道...
Sure. But you know...
-这样不行的  -我们知道这样不行 肯德尔
- this is not okay. - We know it's not okay, Kendall.
我们正在准备公司的回应
We're preparing a corporate response.
我们有公司以外的公关吗
Do we have outside PR?
平克斯不能用了 我们现在有J·普雷斯顿
Pinks passed. We've got J Preston.
不是吧 说真的吗
No, seriously?
她们只是三个令人作呕的白人老妇女
They're three disgusting, old, white dudes.
她们可能只会说自己是贪财的荡妇
They'll probably just say they're money-grubbing sluts.
-雇用她们不是个好的公关策略  -我意思是 你可以说我反社会
- It's bad PR to hire them. - I mean, call me sociopathic,
但是 这一切看起来难道不是有点...
but doesn't this all seem a tiny bit...
与过去几年相比 不是有点奇怪吗
quaint in comparison to the past few years?
他说得对
He's right.
这是文化的飞溅
It's cultural splash back.
我们因为其他人的罪而受到惩罚
We're being punished for the sins of others.
没有人会真的在乎
No one real gives a fuck.
不 不 我们...我们不能等着影响自己消亡
No, no. We... We can't be seen to minimize.
我觉得 我们需要大声快速地宣告
I think we need to loudly and quickly say
这样不行
that this is not okay.
我认为问题是 怎么样才能最快灭掉这个火
I think the question is what closes this down fastest?
我们是觉得这算是个事 我们把它解决了
Do we say it's something and we'll fix it,
还是说这屁都算不上 理都懒得理
or it's nothing and fuck off?
算是个事 肯定会有后果
Something. There have to be consequences.
不 谴责然后撒手不管 这是一个很好的建议
Nope. Condemn and move on. It's just good advice.
如果我们参与其中 他们永远不会满足
If we get into it all, they'll never be satisfied.
这就是胡说八道 这都是因为我
It's bullshit. It's all about me.
这不是真的 这些说法不诚实
It's not real, it's not honest.
他们根本不会在乎这些可怜的贱人
They don't give a flying fuck for these poor bitches.
他们恨的是我
They hate me.
所以 不 谴责然后撒手不管
So, no! Condemn and move on.
明天城里又会有新的新闻上头条的
New circus in town tomorrow.
座谈小组怎么办 肯德尔
What about the, panel? Kendall?
罗曼 我们取消吗
Roman? Do we cancel?
不行 他妈的不行
No! Fuck no!
不 显然不行 不行
No. Obviously not, no.
-我的意思是...  -显然 这样会很棒
- I meant... - Obviously, it'd be great
如果我们继续面对这个事 让一个人
if we do go ahead with it, to, have a person
站出来在这方面谈谈...
who could speak to it in terms of...
要是个女性
A woman.
-格丽吗  - 好吧 我不是法律顾问
- Gerri? - Well, not legal counsel.
这样会给出错误的信号
That gives the wrong sign.
不 我的意思是...这不明摆着有合适的人选吗
No, I mean... It's something of a no-brainer.
我...我不知道 我...
I... I don't know, I...
-拜托 我才刚到这里  -小西
- Come on. I just got here. - Shiv.
你能上台谈谈吗 请你了
Would you? Please?
得了吧 大会不邀请我来参加
Come on. I'm not good enough for an invitation,
突然之间 这事爆了 你就想用这事来堵住...
and suddenly this blows up and you wanna jam it up my...
我他妈的子宫 然后用我的雌激素来消除影响 拜托
fucking uterus and smother it in estrogen? Please.
不 我...我还没有完全了解情况
No, I... I'm not fully briefed.
我们不需要小西 我能搞定
We don't need Shiv. I can do it.
我们能搞定
We can do it.
好吧 我们需要你的帮助
Fine. We could do with your help,
不过 你不帮也行
but fine.
好的 我们走出去吧
Okay. Let's get out there.
-蒙羞之旅吗[带着羞愧走出去]  -是的
- Walk of shame? - Yeah.
大家都出去吧 一切照旧
Everybody out. Business as usual.
那 你想我和瑞亚联系一下
So, you want me to touch base with Rhea,
-探探那边的态度吗  - 不 不 不 不 不
- take the temperature? - No, no, no, no, no.
谁也别去找瑞亚谈话
No one speaks to Rhea.
-除了我和莱尔德 其他人都别  -好的
- Me, Laird, no one else. - Right.
小西 你和我一起
Shiv, you're with me.
该死的"可靠"小姐
Little miss fucking credible?
洛根 你下午6点的预约取消了
Logan, your 6:00 PM canceled.
-还有晚上7:30的也是  -卡塔尔那边呢
- Also, your 7:30. - Qatari money?
他说他会见面喝杯咖啡
He said he'd meet for coffee.
对晚餐持谨慎态度
Wary about dinner.
杰克取消了晚餐
And Jack canceled dinner.
就像操场流言
Playground bullshit.
每个人都在等着看流言是怎么发挥作用的
Everyone's waiting to see how it plays out.
等一下
Hang back a second.
什么事 老兄
What's up, dude?
我想 如果你真的是在搞什么事
I guess if you did have something going on,
你知道的 比如交易什么的 那应该是
you know, like, deal-wise, it's kinda, like,
葬身海底了 对吧
dead in the water now, right?
就像那些游轮上的那些女人一样
Like some of the women that went on those cruises.
肯 我很抱歉 兄弟 我为你感到难过
Ken, I'm so sorry, bro. I feel for you.
-嗨  -你好吗
- Hi. - How are you?
挺好
Okay.
-你呢  -挺好的
- You? - Yeah.
好
Good.
杰米...
Jamie...
-你看了吗  -嗯 这事很不利
- You've seen? - Yeah. It's not good.
-确实  -这对皮尔斯的交易不利
- No. - It's not good for the Pierces,
对代理权争夺战不利
it's not good for the proxy fight.
-我需要和瑞亚谈谈  -我试过打了电话
- I need to speak to Rhea. - I've tried calling.
打了几次
Several times.
我在想 无论如何
I'm wondering, in any event,
由我去接触他们 是不是适合
if I'm the right flavor of person to be reaching out.
我的声誉现在就像货币一样起伏不定
Now my reputation seems to be a fluctuating currency.
但是 年轻的西沃恩 她就像我们能买到的
But, young Siobhan, she's as close to T-Bills
短期国债一样稳固
as we're likely to get.
爸
Dad?
-天啦  -天哪 爸
- Christ. - My God. Dad.
-老天  -爸爸
- Jesus. - Dad?
-你还好吗  -嗯嗯嗯 我们没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah, yeah, yeah. We're fine.
我们没事
We're fine.
-我没事 我没事  -好的 我们没事 谢谢
- I'm fine. I'm fine. - Okay. We're fine. Thank you.
你好
Hi.
对不起 我不能和你一起喝咖啡
Sorry I couldn't meet you for coffee.
我开了非常多的会
I've had wall-to-wall meetings.
不 没...没关系
No, it's... it's fine.
你在躲我们 换了我也会这么做
You're hiding from us. I'd do the same.
你爸爸怎么样
How's your dad?
谣传他就快死了
The rumor mill is saying practically dead.
嗯 他没事 只是...高原反应而已
Yes. Fine. It's... It's the altitude.
所以...
So...
那篇文章 我为所有的小题大做感到抱歉
The piece. I'm sorry for all the fuss.
你知道这些是怎么回事的
You know how these things are.
不 我...其实 我不知道
No, I... I don't, actually.
好的 好吧 会有那么几天...
Okay. Well, for a few days...
你懂的 大家离你而去
you know, people step away from you
就像你在舞池上放了屁一样
like you farted on the dance floor
但是 你挺过去了 没什么大不了的
but you ride it out. It's no big deal.
但你来我这 了解最新情况
But you're here. Checking in.
是啊 好吧 我很惊讶你打电话过来
Yeah. Well, I was surprised that you called.
你属于可以接受的人
The acceptable face.
对
Right.
所以 你知道这篇文章即将发表
So, you heard the piece was coming,
而你还在推进交易
and you're still pushing this?
你一定是非常希望这种情况发生吧
You must really want this to happen.
好吧 我来得容易去得快
Well, I'm easy come, easy go.
还有 其他人都什么态度
And, where is everybody else's head at?
好吧 有些表亲还在读报道
Well, some of the cousins are still reading,
这很令人惊讶 因为...
which is surprising, because...
乔纳森·弗兰岑的新书还没上架
they have views on the new Jonathan Franzen
他们就已经有自己的看法了
three days before it fucking hits the shelf.
保持观望还舒服吧
Comfy on the fence?
是啊
Yeah.
南怎么样
What about Nan?
她很不高兴
She's quite unhappy.
她不喜欢混乱
She doesn't like a muddle.
好吧 如果她有什么问题 或者想缓解什么担心
Well, I'm around if she has any questions,
我就在附近
or to allay any fears.
-当然  -谢谢
- Sure. - Thank you.
我猜我们的第一个问题可能是
I guess our first question might be
有没有任何人在你们游轮上杀过女孩子
did anyone kill any girls on your boat?
没有
No.
从统计学上讲 你知道
And, you know, statistically speaking,
航船上死亡率很高 仅仅是因为酒精的缘故
liners have a high death rate simply because of the alcohol,
以及那些倾向于...
and the profile of the people who tend to...
是的 但事实上 我甚至不得不问...
Yeah, but the fact that I'm even having to ask...
女孩死了 船
Dead girls, boats?
传播出去有些让人不舒服
It's unpleasant on the tongue.
好吧 也许这家人去找另一个投资渠道
Well, perhaps the family would be more comfortable
就舒服了
seeking another source of investment.
我喜欢你爸
I like your dad.
但...
But...
我们现在面临的是什么类型的问题
what sort of a problem are we looking at here?
我们现在是在风暴中心
Are we in the middle of the storm,
-还是说这才只是前奏  -不 我爸向我保证过
- or is this the first raindrops? - No, my dad has assured me
这不是个大问题
that this is not a major issue.
事实上 现在情况很危急
Truth is it's in the balance.
我想我们...他们觉得
I think we... they feel that
如果这只是很久以前的几个烂苹果
if it was just a few bad apples from a long time ago,
那么也许他们可以咬紧牙关
then maybe they can grit their teeth.
嗯 那我们就是一条战线的
Well, that's going to be the line,
-那  -好
- so... - Good.
好了 南会去看你的座谈
Well, Nan is coming to your panel,
所以 我相信你的宣传能帮你
so I'm sure your flacks are getting you all
投球入篮
jumping through hoops,
但是 如果你能把止血带用好
but if you could apply a nice tourniquet,
那 也许我们还可以补救这次交易
then maybe we could patch this up.
嗯 座谈只有罗曼和肯德尔上
Yeah, it's just gonna be Roman and Kendall.
噢 罗曼 好的 可爱的家伙
Right. Roman. Okay. Lovely guys.
-我想也许你可能会...  -不
- I thought perhaps you might... - No.
不 我不上 已经通报了 所以...
No, I'm not, fully briefed. So...
是啊
Yeah.
会向你通报吗
Could you get briefed?
应该会吧
I guess.
-这真的不是我的烂摊子 不该我来清理  -是的 当然
-This isn't really my mess - to clean up. - No. Sure.
但是...我的意思是 我不想过分夸大其词
But... And I mean, I don't wanna overdramatize,
但是南有点打退堂鼓 而你们收买不了我们
but Nan gets cold feet and you can't buy us.
你爸可能会失控 他可能会
Your dad could lose control. He could.
那是真的
That's real.
我在座谈小组上出现 可以有很多不同的身份
There are many different angles to me appearing on that panel.
当然 我明白了 亲爱的 但听着
Sure. I get it, honey. But listen.
我只是想说 积累资金
All I would say is there is a time
需要花时间 花钱也需要花时间
to accumulate capital, and there is a time to spend it.
但是无所谓 我爸以前还在石棉厂当工人呢
But whatever. My dad worked in an asbestos plant.
所以...
So...
这些都是肉汁[意外之财] 对吧
It's all gravy, right?
还有 罗曼 安全的话题是三个R 好吗
And Roman, the safe place is the three Rs, okay?
-好的  -表达遗憾
- Yeah. - Regret.
这事发生在很久以前了
It happened a long time ago.
承担责任
Responsibility.
这是个人行为而非公司行为
Belongs to individuals and not corporations.
补救措施 超级强硬 超级模糊
Remedy. Super tough, super vague.
谴责这样的行为 然后撒手不管 明白了吗
The move is condemn and move on. Got it?
-是的 明白了  -好的
- Yeah, got it. - Okay.
对 如果你在紧急情况下
Right, and if you need to smash glass
需要摔玻璃来表达情绪
in case of emergency,
那就到位了 然后回到会议议题上
it's enough of that and back to the session.
数字时代的家族所有制和企业连续性
Family ownership and corporate continuity in the digital age.
这议题他妈的是什么鸟意思
Whatever the fuck that means.
那 听着
So, listen.
我想也许我应该帮忙做这件事
I think maybe I should help out and do it.
-座谈小组吗  -什么
- The panel? - What?
-是的  -对
- Yeah. - Right,
但是 离开场只有9分钟了
but it's like nine minutes till show time.
小西 不行 我们已经决定了
Shiv, no. We already decided.
是啊 我们都准备好了
Yeah. We're all prepped.
好的 好的 安排两位"每月有毒男性"的
Okay, fine. So, send out the two cover stars
封面明星上场 还有
for Toxic Male Monthly, and,
为什么我们不让泰德·邦迪[连环杀人犯]也上场
why don't we get Ted Bundy up there,
-这样就三个臭皮匠了  -小西 别他妈扯这个
- make it a three-way? - Shiv, don't fuckin' pull this.
-好吗 我们...我们问过你的  -是的 我想过了
- Okay? We... We asked you. - Yeah, and I thought about it,
而且 我改变主意了
and I changed my mind.
-你怎么看  -我吗
- What do you think? - Me?
好...
Well...
-这很难  -这很难
- It's difficult. - It's difficult.
对不起 伙计
I'm sorry, buddy.
你想要人给你打飞机 再吃一粒布洛芬吗
Would you like a handjob and an Advil?
别他妈的模棱两可
Fuck off then.
这招很聪明
It's smart.
小西上场很有用
Shiv works.
很有用吗 突如其来 最后一刻改变阵容 好吗
It's smart? A sudden, last-minute line-up change?
拜托 伙计 他妈的太恐慌了
Come on, man. It's panicky as fuck.
她甚至没在公司里任职
She's not even in the company.
看起来...有点他妈的下等...
It looks... kind of fucking cheesy...
-是的  -老实说
- Yeah. - To be honest.
比如 让我们的象征女神去做这事
Like, throw our token woman at it?
好吧 现在不能两个男的都上场 这样...
Well, it can't be two men up there right now. It just...
不能这样 对吧
It can't. Right?
我的意思是 如果不能按照原计划
I mean, if disruption is an issue,
观众期待的只要是罗伊家的人就行
the audience is expecting just Roys,
所以 也许...也许我们坚持上两个 然后...
so, maybe... maybe we stick at two, and...
换个人下来
someone relaxes.
-罗慕路斯  -怎么 让我下来吗
- Romulus. - What, pull me?
这看起来像是在羞辱我
That looks like a humiliation.
我们可以说你生病了
Well, we could just say you got sick.
不 不 你不能换我 太扯谈了
No. No, you don't bump me. That's bullshit.
去他妈的 恕我不敬 爸 她怎么会在这里
Fuck that. Respectfully, Dad, why is she even here?
因为我他妈是被邀请过来的
Because I was fucking invited.
不 我得上台 好吗
No. I need to be out there, okay?
我们需要坚持到底 你知道吗 一起 一家人
We need to hang tough, you know? Together. Family.
好吧 那我们把康纳也叫过来吧
Okay, so let's just get Connor down here, then?
-是的 把康纳...  -我们都堆一块
- Yeah, get Connor... - We'll all pile on
这样谁的鼻子都不会被揍脱臼 这才是...
so no one's nose gets put out of joint. Is that...
-这才是重要的事  -我会把你的鼻子
- That's the important thing. - I will put your nose
-揍脱臼  -你应该在座谈小组上说这话
- out of joint - You should say that on the panel.
这个笑话很好笑 西沃恩
That's a funny joke, Siobhan.
如果你想知道我真实的想法 我觉得
If you wanna know what I really think, I think
这两个家伙你都应该放弃 我一个人独自上台
you should drop both these two, and I'll do it solo.
有人以为自己是碧昂斯呢
Someone thinks they're Beyonce.
很绝望啊 小西 你知道吗
Pretty desperate, Shiv. You know,
利用这种情况谋取私利
exploiting the situation for personal gain.
我只是在考虑怎么样对公司最有利 好吗
I'm just thinking about what's best for the firm. Okay?
当然 当然 不 那是...
Sure. Sure. No, that's...
这非常显而易见
That's coming through loud and clear.
她我行我素不顾后果 她失控了
She's a loose cannon. She is out of control.
听着 爸 我不在乎
Look, Dad. I don't care.
我可以消除这事的不良影响 我骨子里非常清楚这一点
I can make this go away. I know this in my bones.
我不需要他妈的闪存卡
I don't need fuckin' flash cards.
我没有正式进入公司 所以我有行动的自由
I'm not officially in, so I have freedom of movement.
但是如果你不想要我上 那我也无所谓
But if you don't want me, then I don't give a fuck.
我会去吃龙虾 看看他妈的烤肉
I will go eat lobster and watch the fuckin' roast,
因为都是...都是肉汁 宝贝
because it's all... it's all gravy, baby.
记住关于新闻的两件基本的事情
It's important to remember two fundamental things
是很重要的
about the news.
第一 这是新的
One: it's new.
所有的事情都是新的
All the things that are new.
很多新闻 新闻
The many news. The news.
你男朋友真的很喜欢在那里舔屁股  -第二...
Your boyfriend's really suckin' ass out there. - Two...
等我们上台的时候 我坐在右边
I'm sitting on the right when we're out there.
你知道吗 我可以透过你的毛衣看到你的胸罩
You know, I can see your bra through your sweater.
-你的鸡巴还露在外面呢  -伙计们
- Your dick's hanging out. - Guys.
-不可能...  -伙计们 够了
- There's no way... - Guys, come on.
-专注  -小罗 小罗 小罗
- Focus. - Ro, Ro, Ro.
一会你上台的时候 要不要我帮你
Do you want me to get a booster seat for you,
拿个垫高垫
when you're out there?
真搞笑 你大姨妈流出来了
That's hilarious. Your period just came on.
我们的目标是将我们的新闻报道发展成...
We aim to evolve our coverage into something that is...
不仅充满活力 而且民主
not only dynamic, but democratic.
发展成一些真正适应
And something that truly serves
我们的观众不断变化的需求的东西
our audience's ever-changing needs.
所以 我们想说
And that is why we like to say,
泛美网络 我们为你...倾听
ATN, We hear... for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
非常感谢 谢谢
Thank you very much. Thank you.
-干得好 宝贝  -祝好运 祝好运
- Well done, baby. - Good luck. Good luck.
你好
Well?
下午好
Afternoon.
南呢
Where's Nan?
感谢大家加入我们
Thank you for joining us.
接下来 请把我们温暖的西北风神的欢迎送给
Next up, please give a warm Argestes welcome
罗曼·罗伊和肯德尔·罗伊
to Roman and Kendall Roy,
韦斯达·罗伊科集团的
joint chief operating officers
两位联合首席运营官
at Waystar Royco,
以及政治和企业战略分析师 西沃恩·罗伊
and political and corporate strategist, Siobhan Roy.
欢迎 你很少参与这些 西沃恩
Welcome. You don't do many of these, Siobhan.
不 我...很难邀请到的
No. I'm... I'm hard to get.
我很容易邀请到
I'm exceedingly easy to get.
那 我喜欢这个理念 在数字时代
So, I love this idea of corporate continuity
企业连续性是一件好事
being a positive in the digital age.
但首先 我想给你们一个机会
But first, I wanted to give you the opportunity
回应今天发表的杂志文章
to respond to the magazine piece, which came out today.
-好吧...  -是的 好吧...你说吧
- Well... - Yes, well... Go ahead.
不 不 你说吧
No, no. Go ahead.
我的意思是 我认为这件事对我们来说...
I mean, I think the thing for us is...
我们不想简单地谴责然后撒手不管
we don't want to simply condemn and move on.
你知道 我们会...我们会调查这件事
You know, we'll... We'll want to look into this,
彻底地调查清楚
investigate it thoroughly,
然后绝对会做正确的事
and then absolutely do the right thing.
我想我们对此都有相同的看法
I think we all have the same view on that.
给我们一点启发
And give us an insight.
这对公司来说是艰难的一天吗 西沃恩
Tough day for the company, Siobhan?
好的 很明显 我有幸在围绕着公司成长
Well, obviously I've been, given the privilege of growing up
同时 又能够在公司外面
around the business, whilst also being able
耕耘自己的小天地
to plow my own furrow on the outside.
她在政界工作了十年
She's been working in politics for ten years,
所以 别指望她给你们直截了当的答案
so don't hold out for a straight answer.
我想给你们一个直截了当的答案
I wanna give you a straight answer.
听着 显然 正如你所说 是的 这是艰难的一天
Look, obviously, as you say, yes, it's been a tough day
对公司来说
for the company.
有时候...在公司治理方面 会出现既不是错误
Sometimes there are... not errors, not misjudgements
不是判断错误的情况
in corporate governance,
-但是...  -灾难吗
- but... - Catastrophes?
嗯 不 因为这真的
Well, no, because it's not really about
和公司程序无关 对吧
corporate procedures here, is it?
这是关于做人的品格
It's about human decency
超越了管理结构
that transcends management structures.
我的意思是 你知道的 所以 当这些故事
I mean, you know, that's what's so abhorrent
在任何领域被曝光时
about these stories when they come to light,
都是得如此令人厌恶
in whatever sector.
有时感觉就像
And sometimes it feels like,
"我的天 这种事...无处不在啊"
"my God, it's... It's everywhere."
是的 那...这绝对正确  我的意思是
Yeah, that... that's absolutely right. - I mean,
刚刚的评论...我只想说...
the language... I just would say...
是的 我们不知道
Yeah, we don't know.
现在 我们还不清楚
Right now, we just don't know.
我们还没有启动必要的调查
We haven't started the necessary investigation,
所以刚刚的评论是...
so that language is...
但是 在情绪上 绝对没错
But absolutely, on the sentiment.
我想他是在告诉我 冷静点
I think he's telling me to calm down.
不不不 绝对不是 不 我不是....
No, no, no. Hell, no. No, I'm not....
我...你知道的 如果这件事是真的
I... You know, if this stuff is true,
对受害者而言
doesn't matter to the victim
发生的这些事情是不是孤立事件并不重要 你知道的
if these were isolated incidents that happened, you know,
这是几十年前的事了 对吗
many decades ago, right?
是的 但是 不能因为这事发生在25年前
Right, and just because it did happen 25 years ago,
就只是简单地谴责然后撒手不管了
is not a reason to simply condemn and just move on.
不 不 绝对不行
No. No. Absolutely not.
你知道吧 几十年来 我们一直在积累和维护
You know, we've been accruing and maintaining brand loyalty
品牌忠诚度 这种信任是我们
for decades, and that trust is a result of
了解和尊重
knowing and respecting
-我们的客户的结果...  -不要四处看看
- our customers... - Stop looking around.
你会伤到自己的脖子的
You will hurt your neck.
为了不让这种信任遭到破坏
To compromise that trust,
我们将采取必要的措施来弥补
we'll take the necessary steps to make amends.
你知道吗 我们会不惜一切来弥补
We'll do whatever it takes, you know.
我们愿意做任何人希望我们采取的措施来弥补
We'll do whatever anyone wants.
你知道吗 这是...这是关于完全的无懈可击
You know, it's... it's about being completely unimpeachable.
有时候 公司会养成坏习惯
And sometimes companies develop bad habits,
你需要不同的视角 干净的手
and you need fresh eyes, clean hands,
以及新思路来解决这些问题
and new ideas to address those.
是的 我的意思是 这...对于一家
Yeah, I mean, that... That's, the great thing
我们这样结构的公司来说 非常棒
about a company that's structured like ours.
我们可以在保留核心价值观的同时
We can do that while retaining core values,
进行管理变革
you know, manage change.
他很棒 对吧 他很棒
He's good, right? He's great.
我觉得我有点激进了
I think I'm a little more aggressive.
有时候 我觉得你需要的只是宰杀一头好的老式的恐龙
Sometimes I think you just need a good old fashioned dinosaur cull.
谁是你眼中的大霸王龙
And who's the big T-rex in your sights?
不 我的意思是恐龙的态度
No. I mean dinosaur attitudes.
恐龙的价值观
Dinosaur values.
不 我永远不会追杀我爸
No, I would never go after my dad.
这是其他人喜欢的运动
That's a sport others enjoy.
汤姆 你演讲得不错
Tom. You did good.
对不起我之前没在你身边
Sorry I wasn't there for you before,
但是 你知道 现在 "我们为你倾听"
but, you know, "we hear for you" now.
别担心 你他妈在台上艳惊四座啊
No worries. You fucking shimmered.
-谢谢  -一切都还好吗
- Thank you. - Was that all okayed?
不错 把你女儿带去屠宰场
Nice. Bring your daughter to the slaughter.
告诉老恐龙你打算做什么
Tell the old dinosaur what you were gonna do?
对不起
I'm sorry.
"我们愿意做任何人希望我们采取的措施来弥补"
"We will do whatever anyone wants"?
-是的  -去他妈的 对吧 起作用了
- Yeah. - Fuck it! Right? It played.
就是些空话 又没有媒体在场
It's just words. There was no press anyway,
谁他妈在乎呢
so who gives a shit?
怎么了
What?
-刚刚在台上怎么回事  -我只不过跳了一曲舞
- What was that? - I was just dancing.
我对昨晚妮娅的事感到抱歉
I'm sorry about Nia last night.
-你想做什么都可以  -谢谢
- You can do whatever you like. - Thank you.
我并不是真的想那么做
It's not like I really want to.
-真的吗  -是的
- Really? - No.
因为 说真心话 当我看到你和她说话时
Because, truthfully, when I saw you talking to her,
我想扇她的耳光 对她说
I wanted to smack her in the face and say,
"退后 婊子 他是我的"
"Back up, bitch. He's mine."
你应该这么做的
You should've.
我真的很想见到这一幕
I would've really liked to have seen that.
是吗
Yeah?
你的话太过了 西沃恩
It was too much, Siobhan.
恐龙
Dinosaurs?
是的 过界了 小西过界了
Yeah. It was over the line. Shiv went over the line.
我...我觉得当时很清楚
I... I think it was pretty clear
-我是在说...  -不 是很清楚 是啊
- that I was talking about... - No, it was clear. Yeah.
你折磨了老恐龙 你把他架起来活生生地烤
You tortured the old dinosaur. You barbecued him live?
别他妈惹我
Don't fuck with me!
不 别他妈的打他
No! Don't fucking touch him!
没关系 天啦 爸爸
It's okay. Jesus, Dad.
效果很好 好吗 反应都说很好
It played well, okay? Word is it played well.
-没关系  -小罗 你没事吧
- It's okay. - Ro, are you okay?
拿去
Here.
-你没事吧  -你没事吧
- You all right? - You all right?
是的 我他妈好极了
Yeah, I'm fuckin' fine.
都他妈的离我远点 我很好
Fucking leave me alone. I'm fine.
只是一颗牙齿 我再植一颗就行了
It's just a tooth. I'll get another one.
女士们先生们 作为驱使我们千里迢迢
Ladies and gentlemen, as it's traditional
从家里赶到西北风神的传统活动
to roast us home from Argestes,
西北风神颁奖礼正式开始
it's the Argie awards.
有请今晚的主持人
And please welcome your host for this evening,
泽尔·西蒙斯
Zell Simmons!
好吧 你们好吗
All right. How you doin'?
好了 看看你们这些西装革履的家伙
All right. Look at all you guys with your blazers on,
是从伯灵顿制衣厂来的吗
coming from Burlington Coat Factory?
你们都是在那里买衣服的吗
That where y'all shop at?
我很高兴你们齐聚这里
I'm glad you guys are out here,
解决世界的问题
solving the world's problems.
我没有看到你解决任何事情 傻逼
I don't see you solving anything, jerk-off.
是的 这就像大饥荒的时候
Yeah, that's like a guy sitting on a grain silo
一个人坐在粮仓上 说
in the middle of a famine, going,
"为什么每个人都这么失望
"Why is everybody so down?
他们这里没有WiFi吗"
They don't have WiFi here?"
你跟罗曼说话了吗 他还好吗
Did you talk to Roman? Is he okay?
嗯 他说他不来了
Yeah. He said he wasn't gonna come.
但是...但是他没事
But... But he was fine.
好了 我们看看这里都有谁 看看都有些谁
All right, who do we got here? Who we got here?
我们有... 罗伊一家在这里 你们好吗 伙计们
We got... The Roys are here! What's up, guys!
我操 我希望他不要点我
Shit, I hope he doesn't do me.
喂喂喂 绝不操蛋的董事会允许吗
Ahoy there! Permission to never fuckin' board?
我想这会是一段很长的时间
I think this is going to be a long bit.
我不明白这个传统
I don't understand this tradition.
为什么我们要来受侮辱
Why do we come to be insulted?
这是怎么样的娱乐
How is this entertainment?
我甚至不应该这样开他们的玩笑
I shouldn't even be joking about them like that,
因为他们正忙于...
because they're in the midst of a...
"亲自调查"之中
"hands on investigation".
是的 我听说这里还有很多交易
Yeah, I hear there's a lot of deals going down here, too.
伙计 有人要出售
Man, someone's gonna make a sale.
致韦斯达 我觉得这很棒
To Waystar. I think that's great.
就像兴登堡飞船坠毁一样
That's like the Hindenburg going down,
他们是这样的反应 "哇 氢气飞艇
and they're like, "Yeah, hydrogen blimps.
报名参加
Sign me up!
那就是未来 宝贝"
That's the future, baby!"
不 那是一个可怕的想法 而且比那更糟
No, that's a horrible idea. It's worse than that,
至少在兴登堡飞船上没有人
at least nobody was forced to give a blowjob
被迫为别人口交
on the Hindenburg!
你要去哪里
Where are you going?
-你还好吗  -是的
- You okay? - Yeah.
看看洛根·罗伊 伙计 我爱那个人 伙计
Look at Logan Roy, man. I love that guy, man.
-我的意思是 他是一个非常好的人...  -这很有趣 因为是真的
- I mean, he's a very nice guy... - It's funny 'cause it's true.
滚开
Fuck off.
南
Nan.
-南希  -我们稍后再说吧
- Nancy! - Let's talk later.
瑞亚也来了 当然
Here comes Rhea. Of course.
我们谈谈吧
Let's talk.
我...我希望你没有受到...
I... I hope you're not swayed by...
我的意思是 你感受到了这些温室气氛
I mean, you get these hothouse atmospheres,
-但是 我们没事  -我们再聊
- but we're good. - We'll talk.
-那我们之间没事吧  -没有
- We're good though? - No.
但我们可以解释一下
But we can explain.
听着 这是...这不过是茶壶里的暴风雨
Look, it's... It's a tempest in a tea kettle.
放松 我都是一品脱一品脱地喝的
Relax. I drink them by the pint.
谢谢 我非常放松
Thank you. I am perfectly relaxed.
但是如果你想谈收购的事情
But if you want to talk about it,
-这事吹了  -南
- it's over. - Nan.
-拜托 冷静点  -无非是几个不好的笑话
- Come on. Calm down. - A few bad jokes,
怎么 你就这样屈服了
what, and you bend?
我认为你是比这些帕洛阿尔托刺头们
I think you're made of stronger stuff
-更强大的东西组成的  -这简直无法忍受
- than these Palo Alto pricks. - It's intolerable.
今晚我和家人通了电话
I had a call with the family tonight,
谈了很多问题
on a number of matters,
他们把决定权留到了我手上
and they've left it in my hands.
哪个电话 是...我们打了电话之后
Which call? After... After our call?
瑞亚 我可以问你一件事吗 你有没有
Rhea, may I ask you something? Have you ever had
和洛根·罗伊有过任何沟通或会面
any communication or meetings with Logan Roy
-是我不知道的  -什么
- that I'm not aware of? - What?
没...
Not...
-没有...  -你是想搞清楚
- Not in terms of... - Are you trying to figure out
你的律师会让你说什么吗
what your attorney would let you say?
- 不 我一直都是以...  - 我被蒙蔽了
- No! I have always acted with... - I have been rolled.
我被你们联手骗了
I have been sand-bagged.
这是个很好的协议
This is a good deal!
你13号与洛根谈过
You spoke to Logan on the 13th.
那次谈话的实质内容是什么
What was the nature of that discussion?
我不记得 可能是任何...
I do not recall. It could have been any number of...
我希望你辞职
I would like your resignation.
我不喜欢被人欺骗
I don't appreciate being hustled.
这他妈是个很好的交易
This is a good fucking deal!
你再也不会得到这样优惠的交易了
You won't get a deal like this again.
这确实是个很好的交易
It is a good deal,
而且 除了怎么做对皮尔斯最好
and I have never had anything in mind
我心里从没想过别的事
other than what's best for Pierce.
瞎扯淡
Horse potatoes.
你只为自己工作
You work for Rhea Jarell.
只要我们的利益一致 那就没问题
And as long as our interests were aligned, it was fine.
你会收到律师信的
You'll be hearing from the lawyers.
我还没完呢
I haven't finished.
祝你们两个晚安 终于处理掉这件烦心事了 如获重负啊
Good night to you both. Good riddance to bad rubbish.
你结束这次交易
You turn this down
就是他妈的在害你们全家
and you're fucking your whole family.
我觉得我的家人会没事的
I think my family will be fine,
但是 谢谢你的关心
but thank you for your concern.
-我们走吧  -等等
- Let's go. - Wait!
我们还没完呢 我们他妈的还没有完
We haven't finished! We haven't fucking finished!
你听到我的话了吗
Do you hear me?
我们还没有...停 停车 停车
We haven't... Stop! Stop! Stop!
你...他妈的...停 停车
Do... Fucking... Stop! Stop!
ZIMUXIA.CN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠